MD.FARUQUE AHMED RIZVI



Contact

Address:

M/53, Road-10, Banasree Rampura, Dhaka-1219

Phone:

01934609401 01704934890

Email:

mdbejoy402@gmail.com

Languages

Bangla, English

Hobbies

- Writing
- Playing
- Book Reading
- Internet browsing
- Traveling

Summary

Accountant Assistant with 3 years & In charge data processing department 2 years of experience is seeking to obtain and secure a position which allow me to utilize my Skills, knowledge and abilities, which include but are not limited to: financial auditing, banking knowledge, computer Skills, entering and retrieving data, database queries, generating reports, planning, managing, communicating Skills, and customer service.

Skills

- Bookkeeping
- Bank reconciliation
- Annual accounts
- Invoicing & expenses
- Monthly payroll
- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Database processing

Work Experience

In charge data processing department – 5/2016 to 8/2018

Exquisite Ict Itd.- Mirpur 6, Dhaka

- Web data research
- Data entry quality checking
- Information verification of reported news for news portal
- Assistant Accountant/ HR Admin Officer 09/2018 to Current---

Sthapati Associates Itd: - Banasree, Rampura, Dhaka-1219

- Good handling of account division
- Bank reconciliation
- All bill checking
- Information verification of reported site project
- Site project handling
- Submit report for daily all project & office
- HR division handling good quality

Education

Kushtia Govt. College - M.B.S (Masters)— 2012

Kushtia Govt. Collage - B.B.S (Honor's)— 2008-2011

Kumarkhali Degree Collage-HSC- Business Studies- 2007

Alauddin Ahmed Secondary School – SSC -Business Studies - 2005